CARLOS PROSOPIO

11031 sw 152nd Ct, Miami, Fl 33196 | C: 786-234-8413 | cpros003@fiu.edu

SUMMARY

Highly motivated Graduate in the technology field, adept at resolving complex issues, level-headed and calm in stressful situation. The minimal work experience I have, I make up with side projects I've tackled by myself, and with the 4 years of Software/Technology course work.

SKILLS

- Meticulous attention to detail
- Project evaluations
- JSON/XML
- C/C++
- Java

- Python
- Team player mentality
- Critical Thinking
- SOL
- PHP

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE | SPRING 2020 | FLORIDA INTERNATION UNIVERSITY

- Major: IT (Software)
- · Related coursework: Calculus, Physics, Programming 1-3, Database Management, Software development, Python Programming, Database Administration

ASSOCIATE OF ARTS | 2017 | MIAMI DADE COLLEGE

- · Major: Computer Science
- · Related coursework: Microsoft, Excel, Java, C, C++

EXPERIENCE

DATABASE PROGRAMMER | 2/2020 - CURRENT

- Develop and maintain databases
- Manage and sort large amount of data
- QA and handle sensitive research data

IT TECHNICIAN | 10/2019-2/2020

- Maintained, and administrated Windows server 2012, 2008, and server 2019.
- Lead the development of Windows images to be deployed a various costumers' companies.
- Troubleshooting servers, workstations and software's, on a daily.
- In charge of my own 2 Company sites, performed their daily IT checkups.

CYBER SECURITY CO-LEAD UPSILON PI EPSILON | 02/2019-04/2019

- · Implemented various Kali Linux tools [Nmap, WireShark, Metasploitable]
- · Performed successful SQL Injections, Man in the middle, and Denial of Service attacks, all inside a safe and controlled environment.

SALES ASSOCIATE | INMOTION ENTERTAINMENT | 07/2018-05/2019

- · Processed cash and credit transactions through company POS system.
- · Organized merchandise for sales floor restocking and customer shipments.
- Provided customers with unparalleled service and support for both in stock and back-ordered items, including placing special orders and calling other stores to find desired merchandise.